

- 0428 879 458
- <u>smlxm08@gmail.com</u>
- linkedin
- Github
- Melbourne VIC

EDUCATION

Diploma of IT (2024)

Academy of Interactive Technology

Bachelor of Commerce (2021)

Monash University
Majoring in Finance

VCE (2014)

St Monica's College 93.90 ATAR

TECH SKILLS

Microsoft Office	CSS	MongoDB
JavaScript	React	Node/Express
HTML	Flask	PostgreSQL
Github	GIT	Python

MICHELLE LIANG

ABOUT ME

I have a Bachelor of Commerce in Finance and a Diploma of IT, along with experience in customer service, management, and problem-solving. In my current role as a Direct Lending Advisor at NAB, I help customers with mortgage servicing and loan applications, using both analytical and people skills. Prior to this, I spent over two years co-running a small food business, where I handled operations and customer relations until an opportunity arose to transfer ownership to prospective buyers. I'm passionate about learning and technology, and I'm looking to contribute my skills in a role that offers growth and new challenges.

RECENT WORK EXPERIENCE

NAB | Direct Lending Advisor | 2024 - Current

A member of NAB's Personal Direct Team, helping customers over the phone with mortgage servicing inquiries and writing loan applications. Experienced in understanding customer needs and handling lending processes accurately and efficiently. The role involved attention to detail, following regulatory guidelines, and building good relationships with customers while providing great service.

<u>nology | 2023 - 2024</u>

After completing my IT Diploma, I joined a software training program to enhance my technical skills. As part of the capstone project, I collaborated with a team to develop new features for a student metrics application, which tracks performance, assessments, and feedback. Using a tech stack of MySQL, TypeScript, NestJS (backend), and React (frontend), I contributed by building a form feature for students to update their personal details and refactoring and testing the related API endpoints.

Seafood on Evans | Co-owner | 2021 - 2023

After graduating, my partner and I jumped into running a Fish and Chip shop, hoping to actively apply our commerce degrees to grow and nurture a small business. Key responsibilities included customer service, team mentoring, finances, budgeting, marketing, and stock management. Operations and sales improved, and we managed to sell after two years at a capital gain.

KEY IT PROJECTS

Portfolio Website Link

Visit my portfolio site to see more about me and all the projects I've worked on during my IT diploma!

FEATURED PROJECTS

Wedding Planner Terminal App

PYTHON/BASH

Key features:

- Terminal Application to assist with wedding planning
- Outputs wedding vendor recommendations
- Creates a budget outline and scheduled to do list for users

NightSky API

PYTHON/FLASK

Key features:

- An API for viewing astronomical events in Australia
- Connected to PostgreSQL database
- Includes just under 30 user endpoints with detailed documentation

MERN Full Stack Wedding Invitation

MongoDB/Express/React/Node.js

Key features:

- Fully responsive design, accessible on mobile,
 tablet and pc
- Authentication via JWT token
- RSVP system through form submissions
- Guest List management

Full Stack Employee Management App

SpringBoot/React/SQL/GCP

Key features:

- Employee page to add employees and view, edit, and delete existing employees
- Search function to filter employees
- Toast notifications for successful requests
- Deployed on Google Cloud Platform using Cloud SQL,
 Google App Engine and Kubernetes